Sheldon, you're wrong.
Wolverine was not born
with bone claws.
Howard, you know me to be
a very smart man.
Don't you think
if I were wrong, I'd know it?
Okay, first of all...
Give it up, dude.
You're arguing
with a crazy person.
I'm not crazy.
My mother had me tested.
Hey, guys.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
It's new comic book night.
Yeah, but since you and Penny
finally hooked up, we thought
you two would be having
bouncy naked yum-yum night.
There's more to life
than sex, Raj.
Okay, who had "Leonard
flames out with Penny
- in less than 24 hours"?
- I did.
Nothing flamed out.
We don't have to have sex
every night, you know.
You don't have to,
but it's highly recommended.
Yeah, take advantage
of that window of opportunity
before it slams shut
on your little dinky.
It's not a matter
of opportunity.
We're getting to know
each other.
There's a learning curve.
What's there to learn?
You get naked, do nasty
things to each other,
then somebody makes
scrambled eggs and salami.
Easy peasy.
Perhaps what Leonard
is obliquely referring to
is the occurrence of some sort
of sexual dysfunction.
Okay, who had
"Leonard gets a floppy disk"?
Oh, a clever--
albeit obsolete, euphemism
for insufficient blood flow
to the male sex organ.
(chuckles)
Nothing like that happened,
all right?
The sex was... just fine.
Just fine?
Oh, dude, the fourth Harry
Potter movie was "just fine."
I'm not saying it was bad.
I'm just saying it...
wasn't great.
Okay, when you say
"it wasn't great,"
do you mean for both of you?
Because we can totally see
it not being great for her.
Am I right?
Oh, yeah.
To tell you the truth,
I think we were both a little--
I don't know...
Disappointed? Let down?
Ashamed? Horrified?
Repulsed?
All I know is, it wasn't the wa
y I dreamed it would be.
(scoffs)
Sex is never the way
Idream it's gonna be.
Because in your dreams
you're a horse from the waist down.
Excuse me,
Wolverine: Origin.
Miniseries issue two, page 22.
Retractable bone claws.
If you people spent less time
thinking about sex
and more time concentrating
on comic books,
we'd have far fewer of these
embarrassing moments.
# Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state #
# Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! #
# The Earth began to cool #
# The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools #
# We built the Wall #
# We built the pyramids #
# Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery #
# That all started
with a big bang #
# Bang! #
BBT S03E02 "Jiminy Conjecture"
by Mikhel
Sheldon, dinner's here.
SHELDON:
Tandoori Palace?
No, we went somewhere new.
You're good-naturedly
ribbing me, aren't you?
No, look, Mumbai Palace.
Why?
Why would we change?
We had a perfectly good palace.
Tandoori Palace is our palace.
Trust me, this will be
just fine.
(scoffs)
You are the authority
on "just fine."
(snickering)
What's that supposed to mean?
Yeah, exactly.
"Not bad, but not great."
(stifled chuckles)
What are they talking about?
I don't know
I know.
As I'm sure
you're aware...
Duh-duh-duh-duh
duh-duh.
If that's Morse code,
that's terrible.
As I was saying,
you and Leonard had
sexual encounter. a disap
pointing
Earlier this evening,
Leonard characterized it
as "just fine."
So what you're seeing
here is a continuation
of the mocking that followed.
Okay, yeah, well,
I'm just gonna go
eat my dinner elsewhere.
Maybe an airplane
headed for a mountainside.
Penny, wait.
Aah!
What is wrong with you?
(door slams)
I sense I may have crossed
some sort of line.
Yeah, you...
No, don't tell him
.
Let's see if he can
figure it out.
Ugh, I am so embarrassed!
Please don't be mad.
What did you tell them?
Nothing bad, just that
last night was fine.
Fine? You said it was fine?
Yeah, it's a perfectly
good word.
You put it in front
of "wine" or "dining,"
and you've really got something
.
Okay, well, let me ask you this:
How was last night for you?
It was... okay.
Okay?
Yeah, it's a perfectly
good word.
I mean, you put it
in front of "dokay"
and you really got something.
All right, look,
let's not overreact, you know?
For a lot of couples,
it takes time
to get to know
each other's rhythms.
Learn what the other person
wants and likes.
So, you've been
through this before?
No.
Okay-dokay.
You know, I think this is
one of those things where
talking about it is not
going to make it better.
Want a glass of wine?
So much.
Okay.
See, we should've
done this last night.
You know, have a little wine,
take the edge off.
Actually, ethyl alcohol
inhibits electrical conduction
in the nerve cells and
stimulates reuptake receptors
of inhibitory neurotransmitters
like gamma-aminobutyric acid.
Don't talk, just drink.
No, you're misunderstanding
A shiksa goddess
isn't an actual goddess
And we don't pray to them.
We prey on them.
Whatever, dude.
The point is, Leonard's
got one and you don't.
Is this it?
It was inappropriate to discuss
Leonard and Penny's sex life
in front of Leonard and Penny.
Oh, good!
(sighs with relief)
Now I can eat.
(cricket chirping)
What's that?
Sounds like a cricket.
Hang on.
(cricket crping)
Based on the number
of chirps per minute
and the ambient temperature
in this room,
it is a snowy tree cricket.
Oh, give me a freakin' break.
How could you
possibly know that?
In 1890, Emile Dolbear
determined that there was
a fixed relationship
between the number
of chirps per minute
of the snowy tree cricket
and the ambient temperature.
A precise relationship
that is not present
with ordinary field crickets.
How do you know what the exact
temperature of the room is?
Under the terms of my roommate
agreement with Leonard,
I've had unilateral control
of the thermostat
ever since the sweaty night
of '06.
Okay, you were right about
wolverine and bone claws,
but you're wrong
about the cricket.
Howard, don't embarrass
yourself.
The science chirps for itself.
(chuckling):
Humorous word play.
No, no, not this time.
I know insects, my friend.
I spent many
childhood years
capturing them with nets,
putting them in glass jars,
sticking pins through them,
mounting them on corrugated
cardboard with Dymo labels
underneath, identifying
the genus and species.
In Latin.
Oh, dude, you are never
getting a shiksa goddess.
(cricket chirping)
Thatis a snowy tree cricket.
Oecanthus fultoni.
I was done with Latin
by fifth grade.
Okay, okay, tell you what.
I am willing to bet anything
that's an ordinary
field cricket.
I can't take your money.
What's the matter, you chicken?
I've always found that
an inappropriate slur.
Chickens are not, by nature,
at all timid.
In fact, when I was young,
my neighbor's chicken got loose
and chased me up the big elm
tree in front of our house.
.
Chickens can't climb trees
Thank God.
Okay,
I believe a chicken
made you his bitch.
But the cricket thing,
I don't buy.
Bet me.
Fair enough.
What stakedo you propose?
I will put up my
Fantastic Four number 48,
first appearance
of Silver Surfer
against your Flash 123,
the classicFlash
of two worlds issue.
All right, you have a wager.
Hmm.
Great.
Now how are you going to
settle it, hmm?
There is no way
to determine the species
of the cricket
without examining it.
(cricket chirping)
(chirping continues)
I wonder what the non-pathetic
people are doing tonight.
(cricket chirping)
More wine?
Hit me.
I don't see anything.
Shh!
(cricket chirping)
Hallway.
(groaning)
One at a time.
(deep growling)
What was that?
My stomach.
Indian food doesn't
agree with me.
Ironic, isn't it?
Shh!
(chirping resumes)
(whispering):
Elevator shaft.
(chirping)
Help me open it.
Are you crazy?
We can't go down an empty
elevator shaft.
Fine, if you don't
want to proceed,
then you forfeit the bet,
and I'll take possession
of your Fantastic Four.
Let's open her up.
Are you bothered that I can
so easily manipulate you?
Don't push me, Sheldon.
I may be small, but I took
kung fu when I was 13,
and I remember
a good deal of it.
Oh, really?
Well, I grew up
with an older brother
and a very contentious
twin sister.
And I believe I could
easily best you
in any physical confrontation--
be it noogies, swirlies
or the classic
"Why are you hitting yourself?"
Ooh, big talk from a man who
was once treed by a chicken.
(both chuckle)
What are we drinking now?
Peppermint schnapps.
Why would you buy
peppermint schnapps?
Because I like peppermint,
and it's fun to say schnapps.
(both laugh)
Hey, Leonard?
What?
Schnapps.
You're right
, that is fun.
Be careful.
SHELDON:
If I were not being careful,
your telling me to be careful
would not ke me careful.
(cricket chirping)
Stairwell.
SHELDON:
Uh-oh, flashlight went out.
I need some batteries.
Fellas?
Hello?
It's really dark down here.
(vomiting)
Oh, sweetie.
You really can't hold
your liquor, can you?
I'm okay.
Just a little mouthwash,
and then I'm gonna rock
your world.
(vomiting)
Are you okay?
Ugh, Toby, what did you do
in a past life
to be so disgusting now?
His name isn't Toby
Toby is an absurd name
for a cricket.
What would you name him?
An appropriate cricket name.
For example, Jiminy.
All right,
Sheldon, here we go.
Kleingast's Field Guide
to North American Insects.
Hey, Toby.
Right here.
See it?
The common field cricket,
AKA Gryllus assimilis,
which is Latin
for "suck it, you lose."
Hang on.
Voil?.
The snowy tree cricket.
AKA Oecanthus fultoni,
which is Latin for
I'll suck nothing.
Of course I'm joking
because the Latin for that
isnihil exsorbibo.
That is not Toby,
this is Toby.
Raj, what do
you think?
Oh, I really don't care anymore
God, I had the most
horrible night.
What happened?
Obviously another carnal fiasco
with the shiksi goddess.
Shiksa. Shik-sa.
Forgive me.
Yiddish was not spoken
in east Texas.
And if it was,
it wasn't spoken for long.
Yeah, fine, whatever.
The point is,
you're wrong again.
We haven't established
that I'm wrong once.
All right.
Tell you what.
Let's go down
to the Entomology
Department
and let Professor
Crley tell us
what kind of cricket
Toby is.
SHELDON:
He's a snow
y tree cricket,
and his name
is Jiminy.
I bet I could throw
a rock in this room
and come up
with three better friends.
Holy crap.
It's like Silence
of the Lambs down here.
(screams)
Don't do that!
You're such a girl.
They're just bugs.
Yeah, well,
I don't like bugs, okay?
They freak me out.
Interesting.
You're afraid of
insects and women.
Ladybugs must render
you catatonic.
It was a joke.
I made it to lessen
your discomfort.
You're welcome
(footsteps)
(chuckling): Don't knock.
Just walk in.
Why be polite to the world's
leading expert
on the dung beetle?
Excuse me,
are you Professor Crawley?
Who wants to know?
I'm Dr. Cooper
from the Physics Department.
Couldn't wait, huh?
I'm sorry?
I haven't even packed yet,
and you're already
measuring my lab
for one of your godless
laser machines.
No, you don't understand.
We just want to ask you
a question.
Let me ask you one first.
What's a world renowned
entomologist
with a doctorate
and 20 years of experience
to do with his life
when the university cuts off
the funding for his lab, huh?
Ask rhetorical questions
that make people
uncomfortable?
(sarcastic laugh)
What's your deal?
Are they planning to outsource
my job to Bangalore?
I'm from New Delhi.
Maybe you should find
another entomologist.
No, no. We're here.
Let's settle this.
Professor, can you identify
our cricket?
Of course I can.
I can identify every insect
and arachnid on the planet.
Not that
that's going
to keep me from having to move
in with my daughter in Oxnard.
And we're not talking
Oxnard at the beach. No!
We're talking
Oxnard
in the onion fields.
Well, could you
look at Toby?
Toby?
What a stupid name
for a cricket.
Told ya.
It's a field cricket.
Yes!
No, no, wait.
Dr. Crawley, are you sure?
Young man, I've been
studying insects
since I was eight years old.
You know what
they used to call me
in school?
Creepy Crawley.
Cruel as that may be,
that is not in itself
a credential.
Let me show you something.
See that?
That's a Crawley's dung beetle
I discovered it after spending
six months slogging
through a Bornean rain forest,
while my wife
was back home
shacking up with a two-bit
ornithologist
who lives on a sailboat
and likes to wear
boot-cut jeans!
So, when I tell
you that that's a common
field cricket,
you can take that
to the damn bank!
Cause God knows I can't
Well, apparently,
I was wrong.
Congratulations.
Enjoy Oxnard.
I'm sure your daughter's
looking forward to having you.
Oh, hey, Sheldon.
What you got there?
A new comic book?
Old comic book.
I just retrieved it
from my safe deposit box.
What do you have a safe
deposit box for?
Old comic books.
I lost this
to Wolowitz
in an ill-considered
cricket wager.
What, do they have
Wii cricket now?
That can't be very popular.
Penny, I'd rather
not talk about it.
Well, if it makes you feel
any better,
I'm not feeling so hot either.
Why would that make
me feel better?
I don't know, empathy?
Anyway, I'm just saying,
that you're feeling upset
about something with Howard,
and I'm upset about something
with Leonard.
Yes,
yes, the disappointing
sex.
That's an inexac
t parallel.
You and Leonard can always
return to being friends,
whereas I can never
return to a state
in which Wolowitz
has not bested me
like Mrs. Riley'
s chicken.
What's Mrs. Riley's chicken?
A chicken that was owned
by Mrs. Riley.
Okay, forget the chicken.
Well, I wish I could.
No, no.
You may be right
about me and Leonard.
Of course I'm right
What are the odds I'd be
wrong twice in one week?
No, I mean, we can always go
back to being friends.
I just said that.
This conversation has
started to circle.
Meeting adjourned.
Hello.
Hey.
What's going on?
Oh, you'd like to catch up
on the events of the
day. All right.
Well, there was a half-hour wait
at the bank
to get into my safe deposit box,
I was forced to talk to Penny
about your sexual problems,
and, oh, yes,
in a moment filled
with biblical resonance,
pride wenteth before my fall,
causing my Flash 123
to goeth to Wolowitz.
Wait a minute.
You talked to Penny
about our sex life?
Leonard, it astonishes me
how you continually fixate
on the trivial.
I lost a bet to Wolowitz.
Right, right.
You're saying you talked
to Penny?
Ye-Yes.
Interesting.
Hardly.
Excuse me.
Have I crossed some
sort of line again?
Little bit.
Hmm.
Ah, who cares?
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Uh, what did Sheldon
say to you?
Not a lot.
Just that we always
have the option
of going back
to being friends.
Is that what you want?
I don't know.
I mean, you have to admit
things seemed simpler
when we were just friends.
I guess.
It would take
the pressure off.
It would, wouldn't it?
So, we'll just be friends.
Good.
Come here.
Hmm.
Okay-dokey
www.tvsubtitles.net